[
  {
    "question": "阅读短文首字母填空并回答问题",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "Tom and his mother are s(   ) at the table. They are having their lunch.",
    "answers": ["sitting"]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"I don't like this soup. I don't want to eat it, \" says Tom and puts down his s(   ).",
    "answers": ["soup"]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"All right. Don't eat is then.\" His mother says.",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "After lunch Tom and his mother go to the farm and work hard there. In the evening Tom's mother gives a b(   ) of soup to Tom for dinner. ",
    "answers": ["bowl"]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"Oh, how delicious!\" says Tom. ",
    "answers": [""]
  },
  {
    "question": "\"It's the same soup,\" says his mother with a s(   )",
    "answers": ["smile"]
  },
  {
    "question": "回答问题:4. What does Tom's mother give him for dinner?",
    "answers": ["A bowl of the same soup", "A bowl of the same soup."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Dad drives his car to work every day. （改成一般疑问句，肯定回答）",
    "answers": ["Does Dad drive his car to work every day? Yes, he does."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Alice often plays \"badminton\" with me.（引号部分提问）",
    "answers": ["What does Alice often play with you?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Enjoy yourself at the party.（改为复数句）",
    "answers": [
      "Enjoy yourselves at the party.",
      "Enjoy yourselves at the parties."
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "There is \"a\" bowl of food on the boat.（引号部分提问）",
    "answers": ["How many bowls of food are there on the boat?"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Do some warm-up exercises before you go into the water. （改为否定）",
    "answers": ["Don't do any warm-up exercises before you go into the water."]
  },
  {
    "question": "Ella is shaking the tree. （改为一般现在时）",
    "answers": ["Ella shakes the tree."]
  }
]
